生活大爆炸 前情提要...
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
和女朋友同居?
Cohabitation with my girlfriend?
这件事有点复杂啊
That's a great deal to process.
嗯?
Hmm?
就五个星期而已
It's only for five weeks.
让我用科学理论来说服你
Let me appeal to the scientist in you.
既然我们只有五周的期限
Given the five-week end date,
不如刚好把这看作是一个实验
isn't it the perfect opportunity to consider this an experiment
用来收集有关我们兼容性的数据
and collect data on our compatibility?
别想用这种甜言蜜语诱惑我
Don't try luring me in with sexy talk.
好啵
Okay.
"星际迷航 初代"里
Star Trek: The Original Series.
企业号有一个探索新世界的任务
The Enterprise was on a five-year mission
就是为期五年的
to explore new worlds.
你就把同居当做是
Think of this as your personal
你自己的探索新世界任务 为期五周
five-week mission to do the same.
你看 这种甜言蜜语才能吸引到我
Oh, you want to lure me in with sexy talk, that's how you do it.
不如你们去对面住
Okay, why don't you guys stay across the hall
我们住这边
and we will live here?
很好 我同意了
Very well. I'm on board.
- 真的吗?  - 是的
- Seriously?  - Yes.
我接受这个为期五周的
I accept this five-week mission
与我女朋友分享居住空间的任务
to share a living space with my girlfriend.
哦 这太让人激动了
Oh. This is so exciting.
不要太惊讶 星际迷航里的任务
Well, now, don't be surprised if, like Star Trek,
在第三部就结束了
it's canceled in three.
现在
我有点犯晕
Okay, I'm confused.
机器人先生是哪一个?
Which one is Mr. Robot?
我给你个提示
I'll give you a hint.
我们现在看的是超胆侠
We're watching Daredevil.
能麻烦你俩告诉Amy
Will you two please inform Amy how much you enjoy
严格执行卫生间时间表有多享受吗?
adhering to a strict bathroom schedule?
- 做不到  - 我不干
- Can't.  - Won't.
- 一点不享受  - 不享受
- Didn't.  - Don't.
我告诉过你了
I told you,
你不可能控制生活的方方面面
you can't regulate every aspect of our lives.
可能啊 只要你能俯首甘受命运就好
I can if you'd just roll over and accept your fate.
很抱歉把矛盾带到了这里
I'm sorry for bringing this over here.
信我吧 我特别了解你俩现在的感受
Believe me, we know what you're going through.
而且我... 我们能传授的最好方法就是
And I... I think the most helpful thing we can tell you is
不要反悔
no backsies.
Sheldon 我特别理解
Sheldon, I understand
你喜欢让所有东西整齐排放的心情
that you like things a certain way
我也愿意做出让步
and I'm willing to make some concessions,
但是你也得学会妥协让步
but you have to be open to compromise.
她说得对 这很合理
She's right. That's reasonable.
看看谁才是最大的妥协家
Oh, look who's in favor of compromise,
和Leonard Hofstadter结婚的女人
the woman who married Leonard Hofstadter.
嘿 她才没有妥协
Hey, she didn't compromise.
她只是定下心了 这是有区别的
She settled. There's a difference.
说得对 宝贝
Yeah. You tell him, babe.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第十季第5集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 压力山大酥
校对: 猫呗赶公交
翻译: AU薇 六遇 言小默
你和Bernadette打算什么时候出门?
What time do you and Bernadette head out?
我一到家就走
As soon as I get home.
我们想天黑之前赶到
We're hoping to make it before dark.
我还从来没去过棕榈泉呢
I've never been to Palm Springs.
你们应该去看看
Oh, you should go.
棒极了... 任何地方只要女人的人数
It's terrific. I... I really thrive anywhere
华氏度 相当于32度摄氏度
和温度数上了90... 都能让我生机勃发
the women and the temperature are over 90.
我不知道
I don't know.
如果想看大汗淋漓的老人家的话
If I want to watch old people sweat,
直接和我印度的家人视频就好了
I can just FaceTime my family in India.
你和Bernadette
It's nice you
一块出去度假 真是太棒了
and Bernadette are getting away.
她想在宝宝出生之前
Well, she wants us to spend more time together
多花点时间过二人世界
before the baby comes.
那你这会儿还在这儿买漫画书?
So then what are you doing here buying comic books?
他想在宝宝出生之前
Well, he wants us to spend more time together
多花点时间过二人世界
before the baby comes.
和别人住一块 就一定会有冲突
When you live with someone, there's gonna be conflict.
你们得保持沟通
You just have to keep communicating.
我愿意沟通
I'm open to that.
好啊 首先
Okay. Well, for starters,
把我俩的牙刷放在同一个牙刷架里
there's nothing wrong with keeping our toothbrushes
根本没有什么大不了的
in the same holder.
Sheldon 你什么想法?
Sheldon, what do you say to that?
我觉得我们还是再找另一半吧
I think we should see other people.
啥?!
What?!
作为一个男性 我具有让我的DNA永垂不朽的
Well, as a male, I have an evolutionary drive
进化学意义上的驱动力
to perpetuate my DNA.
让我只和一个伴侣在一起是违背我天性的
Restricting myself to a single partner is against my nature.
我们一年睡一次!
We sleep together once a year!
你这就想找别的姑娘了?
You want other partners?
别怪我 怪你的小伙伴 生物学吧
Don't blame me. Blame your pal, biology.
他才是在幕后捣乱的怪物
He's the pervert pulling the strings here.
你想找别人? 那找去吧
You wanna see other people? Go see other people.
我希望那位最好是猴子 这里的猴戏精彩多了
I hope one of those people is a monkey, 'cause this is bananas.
你可以开玩笑 但是再这么发展下去
You can make jokes, but if this keeps up,
他就要搬回来了
he's gonna move back in here.
好吧 咱们让他俩分开待一会儿吧
All right. Well, let's just get them apart for a while
这样比较能冷静下来
so they can cool down.
好的
Good.
然后在他俩再见面之前
Then before we reintroduce them,
我会让他嗅一嗅她的毛衣
we'll give him one of her sweaters
这样他就能重新熟悉她的味道了
so he can get used to her scent again.
所以你才有资格开玩笑?
So it's okay for you to joke around?
不是玩笑 Howard从太空回来的时候
No, that's actually what we did with him
我们就是这么干的
when Howard came back from space.
宝贝 你还好吗?
Honey, how ya feeling?
书上说在怀孕的这个阶段
The book says at this stage of the pregnancy
晨吐的症状会渐渐消失
morning sickness should be going away.
这是个好消息 对不?
So that's good news, right?
现在除了你 更让人讨厌的就是那本书了!
The only thing I hate more than you right now is that book!
看看你呀!
There she is!
准备好迎接通往沙漠又热气腾腾的
Who's ready for a hot,
三小时车程了吗?
three-hour car ride to the desert?
我下一次会吐在你大腿上
Next vomit is gonna be in your lap.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们也不是非得去呀
We don't have to go.
但是这是我俩单独度假的
But it's our last chance to take a vacation
最后一次机会了
that's just the two of us.
不如我们就待在这儿吧?
How 'bout we stay here?
我们不用告诉别人
We don't even have to tell anyone.
来一次秘密家中度假
It'll be like a secret vacation at home.
向朋友们保密...
Keeping secrets from our friends...
这听起来还挺有趣啊
that does sound kinda fun.
听起来不... 性感吗?
Does it sound... sexy?
你刚刚都听到我吐了
You just heard me throwing up.
一点没错
You bet I did.
你真是太奇怪了
You're so weird.
你知道什么更奇怪吗?
You know what's weird?
你现在有没有欲火焚身
How turned on you are right now.
大家总是指责和我同住
You know, people are quick to accuse me
很困难
of being difficult to live with,
但是事实上 Amy和我一样难搞
but the truth is, Amy is just as challenging.
一样难搞
Just as challenging.
是啊
Yes.
和你一样
As you.
没错
Yes.
跟你一样难搞?
Just as challenging as you.
睡觉时
When we're sleeping,
她对着我呼吸喘气
she breathes on me.
有天晚上 我实在受不了 差点带上老婆孩子狗
One night, it got so bad I almost grabbed Toto
躲进防风地窖了
and headed for the storm cellar.
Leonard也对着我呼吸
Leonard breathes on me, too.
这没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
她总是在吐槽她的同事
She's always complaining about people at work.
Leonard也是啊
Well, so does Leonard.
是有点烦人 但死不了
It's kind of annoying, but it's not the end of the world.
你知道吗? 我洗完澡出来的时候
Do you know that when I get out of the shower,
她跟看猪肉一样上下打量我
she eyes me up and down like I'm a piece of meat?
Leonard也这样
You know, so does Leonard.
早上我梳妆打扮完的时候
Can't I just get ready in the morning
他能不能不要跟傻子一样竖大拇指?
without him giving me his goofy thumbs-up?
"嘿"
"Hey."
我懂你
I know.
有时候我更希望别人能看到我的内在美
Sometimes I would just like to be appreciated for my mind.
同意! 太对了!
Agreed! Thank you!
好舒服
That feels great.
当然
Well,
从你耳朵里变出一个硬币
pulling a quarter out of your ear
可不是这双手唯一会的魔术
isn't the only magic these hands can do.
这...这是什么
In fact, wh...what's this
藏在你的脚趾里?!
between your toes?!
你能不能消停两分钟 不要我身上变出钱?
Can you please stop making money come out of me for two minutes?
这是前门的声音吗?
Was that the front door?
听起来好像是
It sounded like it.
天啊 有人进来了
Oh, my God. Someone's in the house.
锁门 快锁门!
Lock the door, lock the door!
- 我们得报警  - 对...
- We should call the police.  - Uh...
我手机放楼下了
I left my phone downstairs.
该死 我的也是
Damn, so did I.
我有ipad! 怎么办
Wait, I have my iPad! What are we gonna do,
给911发电子邮件吗?
E-mail 911?
你只会帮倒忙!
That's not helpful!
你知道我的
You know I rely
一紧张就想讲笑话
on humor in times of stress.
那讲之前提醒一声 因为真的不好笑!
Let me know when you start, because that wasn't funny!
是浴池的声音吗?
Is that the hot tub?
谁会用我们的浴池?
Who would use our hot tub?
说出来你可能会更慌 或者
Well, the answer is both more and less disturbing
不那么慌
than you think.
是谁?
Who is it?
是Stuart
Stuart.
他听见我说我们要出门
He heard me talking about us going away.
可能就不请自来了吧?
I guess he decided to invite himself over?
我们要跟他说点什么吗?
Should we say something to him?
要吧
Maybe. How 'bout,
"嘿 你看起来像一块水煮鸡胸肉" 怎么样?
"Hey, you look like a boiled chicken breast"?
我是指 "你在这干嘛?" 这类的问题
I meant like, "What are you doing here?"
不 这样伤不到他
Nah, that's not gonna hurt his feelings.
为什么他处处挑剔?
Why is nothing easy with him?
听着 关于Shledon 你要明白一件事
Look, here's the thing you need to understand about Sheldon:
他最难相处
he's the worst.
我希望时间和精力就能解决这个问题
I prefer to think of it as high-maintenance.
我还希望我一米八呢
I prefer to think of myself as five-ten,
还不是每条裤子都要卷裤腿
but I still need to get all my pants hemmed.
我早该知道他是这种人的
I guess I should have known what I was getting myself into.
不要灰心丧气
Don't beat yourself up.
你从来没跟别人同居过
You've never lived with anyone before.
- 这倒是  - 第一次同居
- That's true.  - And you're starting out
还是跟Sheldon Cooper
with Sheldon Cooper.
这就像第一次养宠物就养了...
That's like getting your first pet and having it be...
我不知道...
I don't know...
哪种宠物会毁了你的生活?
What's a kind of pet that ruins your life?
你这样只会让我更难受
You're not making me feel better.
即使是我和Penny 刚开始同居时
Look, even when Penny and I started living together,
也会有一个...一个磨合过程
there was a...a learning curve.
但相信我 情况会变好的
But I promise you, it does get easier.
他在浴室贴了一个牌子 上面写着
He put a sign up in the bathroom that says,
"香皂上没有Amy头发的天数"
"Number of days without Amy's hair on the soap."
我懂
Yeah.
我的记录是6天
My record was six.
是我有问题 还是说
Is it me, or is there something fun
看他浮在那里真的很好玩?
about watching him just float there?
可能这就是人们养金鱼的原因吧
Maybe this is why people get fish tanks.
谁把门廊灯打开了?
Who just turned the porch lights on?
还有别人?
Is someone else here?
他们一定是忘了关掉浴池
Hmm. They must have left the tub on.
还好我来了
Good thing I stopped by.
哇!
Ah!
你在这干嘛?!
What are you doing here?!
你又在这干嘛?!
也许Howard和Bernadette说我可以来!
Maybe Howard and Bernadette said I could be here!
他们真的这么说过?
Did they?
回答我的问题！你在这干嘛?!
Answer the question! What are you doing here?!
我今晚没事干
I had nothing else to do tonight.
过去几个月
The last couple of months,
知道他们不在家我就会过来
I come here when I know they're not home.
什么?!
What?!
有一次我躲在树丛里
They heard me in the bushes once,
但他们以为是只浣熊
but they thought it was a raccoon.
我就说浣熊不会喊 "哎哟"
I told you raccoons don't say "Uh-oh."
有天晚上 Leonard呼噜声超大
You know, one night, Leonard's nose whistled so loud,
我就像睡在了铁轨上
I swear it was like sleeping on a train track.
你有没有注意到他的呼噜声总是降A调?
Have you noticed it's always an A-flat?
是吗?
Is it?
好像他现在就在车里打呼一样
It's like his sinuses are right here in the car.
如果我们要继续这样漫无目的地开下去
If we're just going to drive around aimlessly,
至少你可以带我去买个冰淇淋
the least you could do is take me for ice cream.
好 我带你去买
Yeah, I'll take you for ice cream.
看吧 为什么Amy就不能像这样听我话?
Well, see, why can't Amy be that subservient?
女权主义领导者
我们交媾过一次 她就以为自己是Gloria Steinem了
She has coitus one time, suddenly she's Gloria Steinem.
反正 我想冰淇淋店应该
Anyway, I suppose an ice cream parlor will be a good place
是个跟女孩子搭讪的好地方
to meet other women.
拜托 你连跟一个人发生肉体关系的
Oh, please, you're barely interested
兴趣都没有
in a physical relationship with one person.
为什么还要去祸害别人?
Why would you want to confuse and disappoint others?
跟Amy在一起已经唤醒了我潜藏的性欲
Being with Amy has awoken the sexual creature within.
看到街上的漂亮妞
When I see a pretty gal walking down the street, I think,
我也会跟其他男人一样浮想联翩
"hubba hubba" like any other guy.
你要用这张嘴亲你妈妈?
You kiss your mother with that mouth?
你开心就好
'Cause it's fine.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们敬个酒吧?
Shall we toast?
致Howard和Bernadette
To Howard and Bernadette,
还有他们一直没要回去的钥匙
and the house key they never asked me to return.
你说你拿回来了
You said you got it back.
很明显 我说谎了
Well, clearly, I lied.
你公寓怎么样?
So how's your apartment?
不怎么样 断电了
Not great. The electricity's out.
那你怎么不让人来修?
So why don't you get it fixed?
我打电话了 他们说 "交电费!"
I called, and they're like, "Pay your bill!"
如果你需要地方睡觉 我随时欢迎你
If you ever need somewhere to crash, there's always my place.
不了 我不想打扰你
Oh, no. I don't want to be an inconvenience.
你有你的女朋友们 而且...
You've got all your lady friends, and...
其实 我现在单身
Actually, I'm single now.
什么?!
What?!
什么时候的事情?
When did that happen?
我没事 只是选择了分手
It's okay. It's by choice.
好吧 是她们的选择 我很难过
Well, their choice, and it's not okay.
对不起 我不知道
Oh. Sorry. I didn't know.
没人知道 我觉得很丢脸 所以我谁都没说
Nobody does. I was embarrassed so I didn't say anything.
他怎么没告诉我们啊?
Why wouldn't he tell us?
难道我们是那种糟糕的朋友吗?
Are we bad friends?
他正在我们的热水浴缸里喝着我们的酒呢
He's in our hot tub drinking our wine.
好吧 活该他孤独一生
Yeah, he deserves to be alone.
所以你现在是重回情场了?
So you're back out on the dating scene now?
是吧 算是
Yeah, yeah, a little.
那肯定很意思啊 进展怎么样?
Oh, that must be fun. How's that going?
我现在正在跟你泡热水浴呢 所以不咋地啊
I'm in a hot tub with you, so pretty bad.
我是不是就该妥协那蠢卫生间时间表啊
Maybe I should just give in to his stupid bathroom schedule.
不 别那么干
No, don't do that.
- 但你不就妥协了嘛!  - 正是啊!
- But you did!  - Exactly!
你得从我这吸取教训啊!
Learn from my mistakes!
一到早上7点18分 不管人在哪里
No matter where I am at 7:18 a.m.,
我的附近都得有个厕所
there better be a toilet nearby.
可是直接把他想要的给他 这么做简单多了啊
It's just so much easier to give him what he wants.
说是这么说 但是你就想想你已经取得的成就
Oh, true, but think of how much you've accomplished.
谁让他停止给口袋里的零钱消毒了?
Who got him to stop Purelling his pocket change?
我
Me.
谁成功让他把手套以外的东西
And who got him to put things other than gloves
放在汽车手套柜的?
in the glove compartment?
我
Me.
那是连指手套啦
It was mittens.
又是谁让他试了火鸡热狗的?
And who got him to try a turkey dog?
那实际上是Koothrappali
That was actually Koothrappali,
但是我让他把那口吐在我手上啦
but I did let him spit it out in my hand.
你怎么能现在停下呢?
Look, how can you stop now?
那简直就跟电影放到匹诺曹就要变成
That's like walking out of Pinocchio
真正的小男孩的时候走开不看一样
right before he becomes a real boy.
你说的对
You know, you're right.
我也是这段恋爱关系中的一员啊
I'm in this relationship, too.
我得为自己抗议
I need to stand up for myself.
当然啦
Of course you do.
如果他不喜欢的话 他就得搬回这里
And if he doesn't like it, he can move back here.
他倒是可以试试 不过他就得请个好锁匠了
Oh. He can try. He'd just need a good locksmith.
那你想撩谁呢?
Well, who you gonna hit on?
坐在我们前面的妹子也买了草莓味
The girl in front of us got strawberry.
你的最爱
That's your favorite.
不 如果这样的话 我下半辈子就得在打开冰箱
No. No, if we both like it, I'll spend the rest of my life
然后感慨 "哎呀 草莓味没有了" 中度过了
opening the freezer and going, "Aw, no strawberry."
那柜台后面那个妹子怎么样?
What about the girl behind the counter?
呃 她整天都在挖冰激凌啊
Hmm? Well, she spends her whole day scooping.
可能一只手臂比另一只粗壮呢
One arm's probably bigger than the other.
是不是也有可能你其实根本不想认识别人呢?
Is it possible you might not actually want to meet someone?
你真是有大智慧啊
You are truly wise.
谢谢啊
Thank you.
我本来要说
I'd say
超出年龄的睿智 但是你年纪也不小了
wise beyond your years, but you're getting up there.
好吧
All right.
拜托 你到底是怎么了?
Come on. What is really going on with you?
Penny 我要跟你说个故事
Penny, I am going to tell you a story
这个故事我从来没跟任何人说过
that I've never told anyone.
好吧
All right.
我当年13岁
I was 13 years old,
正好大学放春假
and on spring break from college.
跟不上 继续
Not relating. Go on.
他们教不了我数学了 所以我就提前回家了
I came home early because they ran out of math to teach me.
哦 现在我懂了 然后呢
Oh, now I'm with ya. Okay.
我妈在一个圣经学习班
My mother was at bible study.
我走进家里以为家里没人
I walked in the house expecting to find it empty,
然后我听到我父母的卧室里传来了什么声音
and I heard a sound coming from my parents' bedroom.
我打开门的时候
When I opened the door,
看见了我父亲正在和另一个女人发生关系
I saw my father having relations with another woman.
- 这太糟糕了!  - 就是啊
- Oh, that's awful!  - I know.
这也是为什么我每次进门前
It's also why I never open a door
都要敲三次门
without knocking three times.
我是想 第一次是传统意义上的敲门
I mean, the first one's traditional,
然后第二次第三次是为了让人把裤子提上
but two and three are for people to get their pants on.
那后来你爸那事怎么了呢?
Well, what happened with your dad?
我们对视了一下 我跑回了自己的房间
We locked eyes, I ran to my room,
然后我们再也没说起过这事
and we never, ever spoke of it.
你这个可怜的小倒霉
You poor thing.
自从Amy和我住在一起以后
Since Amy and I have been living together,
我们一直在跟我父母以前一样吵架
we've been bickering like my parents used to.
你是怕你会做跟你爸类似的事吗?
And you're afraid you're gonna do something like your dad did?
是的 我得让她现在做好准备
Yes. I need to prepare her now
让她免除以后的痛苦
to save her from pain down the road.
以后的痛苦?
Down the road?
Sheldon 她只是想跟你分享一个牙刷架
Sheldon, she wanted to share a toothbrush holder with you,
而你现在却在冰激凌店里试图撩妹子!
and now you're at an ice cream parlor trying to pick up women!
哎呀 什么事用你这种语气说出来都会变蠢的
Well, anything can sound silly when you put it in that tone.
亲爱的 与其担心未来
Honey, instead of worrying about pain
你有可能引起的痛苦 为什么不试着
you might cause in the future, how about trying
解除你现在带给她的痛苦呢?
to fix the pain you're causing her right now?
我想你是对的
I'm sure you're right.
我觉得我也应该跟你道歉
I suppose I should apologize to you, as well.
好吧
Okay.
看我勾搭其他女人 却根本没考虑到你
That must have hurt watching me look for other women
一定让你很受伤
without ever even considering you.
请一定要理解 你在我眼里
Please understand that I think of you
更像个保姆
as more of a nanny.
把冰激凌吃完吧 好让我把你带回家睡觉
Just finish your ice cream so I can get you home to bed.
我在想这是不是就是做
I wonder if this is what it feels like
Bernadette宝宝的感觉
to be Bernadette's baby.
我不觉得 Bernadette的宝宝可没有按摩喷气孔
I don't know. Bernadette's baby doesn't have a Jacuzzi jet
拍打着我的关键部位
hitting just the right spot.
那些喷气孔是为我的关键部位服务的 不是他!
Those jets are for my secret spot, not his!
你在那里面都干些什么啊?!
What do you do in there?!
反正是放松就对了 你不用知道更多了
It's called relaxing, and that's all you need to know.
现在已经很晚了
Well, it's getting late.
我们是不是该回家了
Maybe we should head home.
你说得对
Yeah, you're probably right.
走吗?
You coming?
嗯 等我一下
Yeah, just give me a minute.
为什么?
Why?
你看你是穿着泳裤的对吧?
Well, you know how you're wearing a bathing suit?
是啊?
Yeah?
我好像没和你一样走寻常路
I kind of went the other way.
你们这俩混蛋给我把这个热水浴缸买走!
You jackasses just bought yourselves a hot tub!
你觉得怎样?
What do you think?
这位子还可以啊
It's a nice enough spot.
如果我要开始为自己抗议的话
You know, if I'm going to start standing up for myself,
这正是我要做的...
this is exactly the kind of thing...
我们回来啦!
We're back!
嗨! 嗨!
Oh, hi! Hi!
哈喽
Hello.
你们怎么样啊?
How you guys doing?
我们挺好的 我觉得
We're doing good. I think
Sheldon有些话想要对Amy说
Sheldon has something he would like to say to Amy.
我想为我今天的行为道歉 那...
I wanted to apologize for my behavior today. It...
那都是不必要的
It was unnecessary.
这位子很暖和啊
This is warm.
还有 我愿意放弃卫生间时间表
Oh, and also, I am willing to forego the bathroom schedule.
真的吗?
Oh. Really?
凭什么她能捞到这么好的事?! 我们从来没有!
Why does she get that?! We never got that!
你想让他回来吗?
Do you want him back?
我很为你们感到高兴
I'm very happy for you.
Amy 你应该知道
Amy, you should know
我从来就没想要约其他女性
I was never really interested in seeing other women.
而为了证明我对我们的关系有多么认真
And to prove how serious I am about us,
我愿意将我们的关系带入到下一个层面
I'm willing to take our relationship to the next level.
Amy Farrah Fowler小姐
Amy Farrah Fowler,
你愿意跟我共享这个牙刷架吗?
will you share this toothbrush holder with me?
我愿意
I would love to.
我们真的
Did we really
需要在这里见证这个吗?
need to be here for this?
你觉得我疯了也没关系 但是我觉得这很感人
Call me crazy, but I found it moving.